woozworld.com 2013-11-12

# Privacy Policy | Woozworld News

Document revised: October 18, 2012

Revised document #10

## 1\. Introduction

Welcome and thank you for visiting Woozworld’s website located at [www.woozworld.com](http://www.woozworld.com/) (the “ **Website** ”). At Woozworld Inc., a company based in Montreal, Province of Quebec in Canada (“ **Woozworld** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”), we are committed to protecting the online privacy of our members and guests of our Website. To that end, we have designed this privacy policy (the “ **Policy** ”) to address your questions and concerns about our practices and principals for personally identifiable information (“ **PII** ”), including how we collect, use and disclose such information.

If you are a minor, your parent or legal guardian (a “Parent”) must review the [Code of Conduct](http://www.woozworld.com/community/code-of-conduct/), the Policy and the [Terms of Use](http://www.woozworld.com/community/terms-of-use/) of the Website with you, explain anything that you may not fully understand and approve them with you. Children under the age of 13 must get their Parent’s permission before giving out any PII to Woozworld. Woozworld offers the Website to the Parents and their children (referred to as “ **you** ”, “ **your** ” or “ **user** ”) in accordance with this Policy. Parents, please help us protect your children’s privacy by instructing them never to provide PII on this Website or any other without your permission.

Woozworld applies its best efforts and generally accepted industry standards to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your PII. We do not collect or keep any PII from you unless you volunteer it. A child’s participation in an activity is not conditional to the child providing more PII than is reasonably necessary for that activity.

This Policy is applicable to the Website and all associated products and services available on the Website. It summarizes Woozworld’s data collection policies and practices on the Website and does not apply to the practices of companies that Woozworld does not own or control, or to people that Woozworld does not employ or manage.

Your use of the Website means that you accept the terms of this Policy. By using the Website, you agree to the collection, use, transfer and processing of PII as described in this Policy by Woozworld. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, please discontinue the use of the Website immediately and at all times.

## 2\. COPPA and PRIVO®’s Privacy Assurance Program

Woozworld complies with the U.S. [Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act](http://coppa.org/) (“ **COPPA** ”). The COPPA requires that we inform the Parents on how we collect and use PII from their children under the age of 13 and that we obtain verifiable consent from the Parent before a child under that age provides PII.

Woozworld participates in PRIVO®’s [Privacy Assurance Program](http://www.privo.com/). As part of this program, Woozworld adheres to the strict personal information collection, use and disclosure requirements of COPPA. PRIVO is an independent, third party organization committed to safeguarding children’s PII collected online, and to helping parents and their children exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. The certification seal posted on this page proves that Woozworld has established privacy practices and has agreed to submit to PRIVO’s oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about the Policy, please contact us at [privacypolicy@woozworld.com](mailto:privacypolicy@woozworld.com) or at (514) 281-8999. If you have further concerns after you have contacted us, you can contact PRIVO directly at [privacy@privo.com](mailto:privacy@privo.com).

## 3\. Collection and Use of Information

When an account is created, the user’s  **month and year of birth** ,  **gender**  and  **email address**  are requested. If the user is under the age of 13, the  **Parent’s email**  is requested instead of the child’s email and Woozworld communicates with the child only through the Parent’s email thereafter. This information is associated to a username and is used for password-reset purposes.

The age and gender are used as aggregate statistical data to gain insight within the Website’s audience. The age is also used, as explained above, to determine if a user is under the age of 13 in order to get the Parent’s email instead of the child’s one.

Your email can be used to identify your account if you contact Woozworld for any questions or assistance. When your email address is collected by Woozworld, you are asked if you wish to validate this email address so that it can be used to communicate with you when required for some of our advanced features as described below. The user’s email address will never be visible in the advanced features. Within the scope of these advanced features, Woozworld will send directly to you communications such as updates, notifications, promotional invitations and news concerning the Website, which can be sent, without limitation, through the games messaging system or through emails. If you no longer wish to participate in such communications you can (i) click the unsubscribe link at the end of each email received, (ii) sign-in to your account and change your communication preferences in the account settings or (iii) send an email to [customerservice@woozworld.com](mailto:customerservice@woozworld.com).

The text entered in the advanced feature called WoozIn, as well as in-game chat and in private messages is filtered through [Crisp Thinking™](http://www.crispthinking.com/) smart filtering system which aims to prevent, amongst other things, the user from exchanging PII such as phone numbers or email addresses with other users.

Depending on the user’s method of payment in our online stores, some additional PII will be requested as described below. We use Secure Sockets Layer technology to protect credit card data during transmission and adopt strict internal procedures to safeguard this information in our system. Our third party payment solution providers are also under contract to safeguard your PII and not to share it under any circumstances. If the buyer is under the age of 13, the Parent’s verifiable prior consent is required for the collection of those additional PII and for the payment by SMS. Upon visiting the SMS tab in the store for the first time, an email will be sent to the Parent’s email address for them to review the Policy and the [Terms of Use](http://www.woozworld.com/community/terms-of-use/) of the Website and accept them, as well as accepting that the child provides additional PII and makes purchases on the Website through SMS. Parents can always change this consent by logging into the account, going to account settings and checking or unchecking the SMS authorization check box which will send an email to the Parent to approve the modification.

## 4\. Advanced Features WoozIn

The WoozIn is the Website social network where users can exchange comments, post their in-game pictures, show their achievements, exchange with friends, post links to YouTube™, iTunes™, and more. An important part of the WoozIn is the notification system that sends you updates of what’s going on in the Website and with your friends.

## Invite a Friend

You can invite your friends to come play and have fun with you in the Website. When you select the “Invite a friend” feature, you just have to enter your first name to identify you to your friend and your friend’s email address. Woozworld does not save or keep this information anywhere in its system after your invitation is sent out.

## Contests and surveys

If you participate in our contests and surveys no PII will be required to do so. If you win a prize within a contest, which needs to be awarded outside the Website, we will communicate with you through the validated email address provided when you created your account and will agree with you how to award your prize. If you are under the age of 13, these arrangements will be taken care of with your Parent and your Parent’s written consent will be required in order to provide us your  **mailing address**  and other PII needed to award your prize.

## Online Stores

We offer the opportunity to purchase products in our online stores. When a user places an order, our third party’s transaction processor will require the following PII for a payment:

  * Ø by credit card: username,  **full name of card holder** ,  **email address** ,  **mailing address**  and  **credit card information** ; or
  * Ø by cell phone (SMS): username,  **cell phone number**  and  **email address**.

After an order online is placed, we send a confirming email message and/or a SMS depending on the payment method. We may also send an occasional email featuring a special promotion or product that may be of interest to you. Any user who prefers not to receive promotional emails can indicate this preference in the account settings. Please note that, for legal reasons and for your protection, it is not possible to unsubscribe from transaction notification confirmation when buying from the Website.

For purchases made by credit card or through a PayPal account, the purchaser must be at least 18 year old and have a valid credit card or bank account.

## Upcoming developments

We are always working on new ideas to make the Website even more fun. We hope to offer you mini-games to be played in the Website. A notification will be sent to validated emails to promote challenges, contests, leaderboard updates, new games and weekly digests.

## 5\. Cookies, IP Addresses and Clear GIFs

A cookie is a small file that we save on your computer’s hard drive and that contains non-personal information. Cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited. They allow you to personalize your pages and they allow us to customize our offerings to you. They help you to participate in some activities or events on the Website. If you leave the Website and return, cookies allow us to quickly display your collected items and game progress upon your return. We also use cookies to help us to count the number of visits on the Website, track which sections of the Website are most visited and find out the length of time spent in the different sections. This information helps us understand which sections and features are appreciated or need improvement. Woozworld does not use cookies for direct marketing or promotional purposes and cookies are not used to collect and share with third parties any PII.

Due to the Internet’s nature and structure, third party advertising companies, such as Google AdSense and others, might use cookies already stored on your computer from previous browsing sessions to deliver advertisements relevant to your browsing history. We use our best efforts to insure that you are not exposed to inappropriate advertising while on the Website. If you come across inappropriate advertising, please send the advertising link at [customerservice@woozworld.com](mailto:customerservice@woozworld.com) and we’ll have it removed from the advertising spaces in our Website.

We collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, which is the automatic number assigned to your computer when you surf on Internet. We may use your IP address (i) to gather statistics on geographical distribution of our users, (ii) as a geographic filter for specific features, advertising or offers per location or (iii) to help us investigate in the case of bad behavior like account theft, hacking or bullying, and provide the information to authorities in the case of a police investigation for a serious crime.

We also use other technology called Clear GIFs to provide us with other important anonymous information, such as when an email has been opened.

Cookies, IP address and Clear GIFs are not connected to any PII.

## 6\. Third Parties

Except for third parties required in operating the Website as described previously and except as described below, we never share PII with people or companies outside Woozworld or sell it. Before Woozworld discloses any user’s PII to a third party as provided herein, the third party agreed to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information.

The only other situations where we may disclose PII to third parties would be to protect the security or integrity of the Website, to take precautions against liability, or to respond to judicial processes, legitimate requests by law enforcement officials or as otherwise required in order to comply with applicable law.

Please take note that the Website may contain links to third party sites (“ **Linked Sites** ”) and any activities you engage in connection with a Linked Site are subject to the privacy policy and terms of use as defined by the operator of the Linked Site. Please read Website’s [Terms of Use](http://www.woozworld.com/community/terms-of-use/) for further details.  **WOOZWORLD DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL LIABILITY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED IN CONNECTION WITH ANY LINKED SITES.**

Woozworld may also share your email address with its affiliated companies so that they can let you know about products that might be of interest to you. However, your consent will always be asked prior to sharing such information. If you would like to stop receiving such product information, you can (i) click the unsubscribe link at the end of each email received, (ii) sign-in to your account and change your communication preferences in the account settings or (iii) send an email to [privacypolicy@woozworld.com](mailto:privacypolicy@woozworld.com).

Finally, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this Website or others in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## 7\. Customer Support

If you contact customer support, you may be asked for your username, your first and last name, your email and/or phone number. The PII provided within a customer service request is not added to your online account information and will not be used for any other reason than to respond to your specific request. If the user contacting the customer support is a child under 13 of age, we will delete the additional requested PII after the request is completed.

## 8\. Communications within Website

Woozworld may, at its sole discretion, record or store communications submitted through messages, bulletin boards, forums or chat rooms and may monitor, filter and review such communications for the purpose of monitoring content, enforcing Website rules, and investigating and detecting unauthorized use of the Website.

## 9\. No Other Information

You will never be asked for any additional PII while using the Website. We provide as many privacy protection measures as reasonably possible to insure that no other additional PII is communicated or exchanged within the Website. Woozworld employees and on-line moderators (known as Woozband avatars) will never ask you for additional PII. NEVER GIVE YOUR PASSWORD UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES. Please be vigilant and report any user attempting to obtain PII or your password by contacting us at [customerservice@woozworld.com](mailto:customerservice@woozworld.com).

## 10\. Modifications

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Policy to accommodate product improvement, new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for any other purposes. We will provide notice to you and post a notice on the Website if these changes have material impact on Woozworld’s use of PII and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent. An updated version of the Policy can be found at all times on the Website. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Policy. Your continued use of the Website means you accept any changes in this Policy. To consult previous version of the privacy policy click [here](http://www.woozworld.com/community/old-privacy-policy/).

## 11\. Reviewing PII

Upon proper identification, you may review your PII, request change or deletion or refuse to allow further collection or use of the information by contacting us at [customerservice@woozworld.com](mailto:customerservice@woozworld.com) or by telephone at + (514) 281-8999. However, if you ask us to delete any required PII for certain advanced features, your access to those features will not be possible in the future.

## 12\. Contacting Us

You can contact us with any concerns with respect to this Policy at:

Woozworld Inc.  
Attention of Privacy Coordinator  
25 Mozart Street East, 3rd Floor  
Montreal (Quebec) H2S 1B1  
Canada  
Tel.: +1 (514) 281-8999  
Fax: +1 (514) 281-5557
